One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The end of the dream, the end of the sea
‫منتهى غايتي، منتهى البحار‬
We all have different places we want to go WE ALL HAVE DIFFERENT PLACES WE WANT TO GO
‫لكل امرؤ وجهة يتولاها‬
But to start we've got to show what we're made of
‫لولا بصيص واحد يبقى‬
We'll be legends, we're gonna take the world by storm
‫ما إن تكشف الأسطورة عن صفحاتها‬
Sparks are flying, NO LIMITS! This is where it starts
‫حماسة متأججة بلا حدود، هلم جرا إلى‬
ONE PIECE!!
‫ون بيس!‬
VORONOI START VORONOI END ALL OF US, I've got a question for you
‫كل واحد منا، لدي سؤال لكم:‬
Have you let the world and all its burdens bring your dreams down?
‫أما زال درب أحلامكم سالكًا؟‬
Every cell in me is getting restless - They're about to blow, oh, it's just too much Every cell in me is getting restless - They're about to blow, oh, it's just too much
‫خلاياي الهامدة تُثار وتفيض حماسةً‬
Still we try, ALL OF US have our own paths we cling to
‫إنما كل واحدٍ منا في مغامرة‬
ALL OF US, I've got something to tell you
‫كل واحد منا، لدي ما أخبركم به‬
ALL OF US, I've got something to tell you If you've got a dream that's worth a damn you've gotta stand tall
‫كل واحد منا، لدي ما أخبركم به ما من معركةٍ نخوضها إلا تحمل العبرة‬
If you've got a dream that's worth a damn you've gotta stand tall
‫ما من معركةٍ نخوضها إلا تحمل العبرة‬
Random clues suddenly fit together
‫وما خُفي في السياق المُتناثر يحمل معنى مترابط‬
Threads of time weaving into an intricate tapestry
‫وخيوط الزمان ستُحاك تارةً أخرى‬
We can't stop the world from turning, it's changing along with every one of-
‫وبنا جميعًا سيتبدل حال العالم على الدوام‬
You almost stepped on us, man!
‫أتعزم دهسنا أيها الأحمق؟‬
My bad, my bad!
‫اعذرني‬
You've certainly grown...
‫بِتَّ ضخمًا...‬
I'm not letting you take Apple Gramps.
‫لن أسلّمك عجوز التفاحة‬
I'd appreciate it if you'd just...
‫هلّا تركتني...‬
let me do my job, please.
‫أُتمّ مهمتي...‬
No can do!
‫في أحلامك!‬
Whoa, now...
‫ويحك...‬
Here we go!
‫سأرميك...‬
Go easy on me...
‫ارفق بي...‬
if you wouldn't mind!
‫رجاءً...‬
Luffy vs. Kizaru
‫لوفي ضد كيزارو‬
Look at him go!
‫طيَّرتُه تطييرًا‬
We gotta run before it's too late!
‫علينا الهرب قبل فوات الأوان‬
Yeah, while Luffy is keeping Kizaru busy!
‫أتفق معكِ، فلوفي يصرف كيزارو عنّا‬
We'll have to be careful carrying Robin!
‫علينا نقل روبين بحذر‬
Where are you going, Atlas?!
‫أين ذاهبة يا أطلس؟‬
I'm going down there to take back control of the pacifista!
‫سأنزل لاستعادة التحكم بالباشيفيستا‬
Otherwise...
‫وإلّا...‬
as soon as the barrier goes down...
‫ما إن نُزيل الحاجز‬
they'll blast us with their lasers!
‫سيغربلوننا بالليزر‬
What a capital idea!
‫هذا أفضل الحلول،‬
Vegapunk's the highest authority on this here island!
‫ليس بهذه الجزيرة من يعلونا سلطةً‬
And whoever controls the pacifista wins!
‫والكفَّة تميل لمن يتحكم بالباشيفيستا‬
Damn right! I'm off!
‫أجل، سأمضي‬
Wait, Atlas!
‫تمهّلي يا أطلس‬
Er, what I mean is...
‫ولكن... أنا...‬
I... I'll go with you!
‫سـ-سأُرافقكِ!‬
There's no way you're going!
‫يُمنع عليك ذلك!‬
Why not?
‫ولمَ؟‬
This whole thing is happening because they're trying to kill you!
‫كيف ترافقها وأصل هذه الفوضى أنهم يبتغون قتلك؟‬
Yes, but...
‫ولكن...‬
Hey, Franky!
‫يا فرانكي-كن!‬
Franky, can you hear me?!
‫أتسمعني يا فرانكي-كن؟‬
Yeah!
‫أجل‬
It seems like Bonney is down there!
‫الظاهر أن بوني عندكم بالأسفل‬
She's alive?! That's great news!
‫أهي حية؟ ارتاح بالي‬
Kizaru kicked her hard—right into the barrier!
‫كيزارو ركلها واصطدمت بالحاجز‬
He kicked her?!
‫أقلت إنه ركلها؟‬
Aren't you a grown man?! How could you let her get kicked?!
‫أيكون معها بالغ مثلك وتُركل؟‬
I get it, man! My bad!
‫الذنب ذنبي أنا فأعتذر‬
I'll go save her right now!
‫سأنقذها حالًا‬
You'd better!
‫عليك ذلك!‬
But there's still the barrier...
‫ولكن الحاجز...‬
That's it! I'm going too!
‫لعلّ ذهابي أفضل‬
What?
‫ما...‬
Edison can deactivate the barrier.
‫يُمكن لإديسون تعطيل الحاجز‬
Hello?!
‫مرحبًا‬
Second Floor Building A
‫الطابق الثاني‬ ‫من المبنى أ‬
This is Sanji speaking!
‫معكم سانجي‬
If you're gonna rescue Bonney, count me in!
‫إن مضيتم لإنقاذ بوني-تشان فسأرافقكم‬
Vegapunk. We've picked up the luggage you mentioned.
‫جمعنا كل أغراضك المطلوبة يا فيغابانك‬
I'll head toward the rear exit!
‫سأتجه إلى المخرج الخلفي‬
Let's all meet up there!
‫لنلتقِ جميعًا هناك‬
Go, go, go!
‫تحركوا، تحركوا، تحركوا‬
Below In the Fabriophase
‫أسفل طابق‬ ‫المختبـــر‬
Oh, crap!
‫ويلي‬
What was that?
‫كأني لمحتُ شيئًا‬
Hey, you there!
‫يا هذا‬
Get a move on! It's this way!
‫عجِّل وتعال، من هنا!‬
Yes, sir!
‫أمرك‬
Guess I'm not safe here, either.
‫ولا هذا المكان آمن‬
Over here!
‫أنا هنا‬
What was that?!
‫ما هذا الصراخ؟‬
Come in!
‫أجيبوا،‬
What's going on?!
‫ماذا يحدث؟‬
You little...
‫يا شقية...‬
Hey, stop!
‫مهلكِ‬
You're...
‫أنتِ...‬
Jewelry–
‫–جولري‬
Town central team! Give me a status report!
‫يا فرقة الوسط، أبلغوني المستجدات‬
W-Well...
‫حـ-حسنٌ...‬
Why, you...!
‫يا بنت الـ...‬
D-Dammit...
‫تـ-تبًّا لها!‬
Report!
‫هاك تقريرنا‬
We've all been turned into children and seniors!
‫تحوّلنا جميعًا إلى أطفال وعجائز‬
Dammit!
‫تبًّا!‬
Stay away from the center of town!
‫لا تقربوا وسط البلدة‬
We believe the pirate Jewelry Bonney is there!
‫الظاهر أن القرصانة جولري بوني مختبئة هناك فتوخّوا الحذر‬
She'll manipulate your age!
‫وإلا تلاعبت بأعماركم‬
It's too heavy!
‫أين مضت تلك الشقية؟‬
Where'd that blasted kid get off to?
‫ما أثقلها!‬
She must be nearby!
‫إنها على مقربة،‬
Find Bonney and take her out!
‫فتقفَّوا أثرها واقضوا عليها‬
Damn...
‫تبًّا...‬
Hey, over here!
‫تعالوا، عثرنا على مطلبنا‬
Sentomaru has been located!
‫عثرنا على سينتومارو!‬
But...
‫لكنه...‬
he's burned to a crisp.
‫متفحِّم...‬
Sentomaru...
‫سينتومارو...‬
S-Sentomaru!
‫سـ-سينتومارو!‬
Bonney...
‫بوني...‬
Run...
‫اهربي...‬
The Marines are coming...
‫البحرية آتية‬
Sentomaru!
‫سينتومارو!‬
What should I do?
‫ما العمل؟‬
Was she there?
‫أعثرتم عليها؟‬
No, sir!
‫كلا‬
Go check that way!
‫مشِّط تلك الناحية‬
Yes, sir!
‫أمرك‬
Can I stay hidden until this all blows over?
‫أسيدركوا مكاني؟‬
Labophase
‫طابق‬ ‫المختبر‬
Hey!
‫اخرج حالًا يا هذا‬
Let us do our job, Roronoa.
‫لنتم مهمتنا يا رورونوا‬
Don't get in our way!
‫لا تعترض سبيلنا‬
It doesn't matter if you hide...
‫اختبئ أينما شئت‬
It doesn't matter if you move around...
‫واهرب حيثما شئت‬
I know exactly where you are...
‫فأنا أعرف مكانك‬
because you stink like an animal!
‫لأني أشمّ عفن الحيوانات‬
You're really going at it!
‫إنك تحسن القتال‬
Zoro! Want a hand?
‫أأساعدك يا زورو؟‬
I'm just... fine!
‫أنا في غنى عن ذلك‬
Just focus on Kizaru!
‫ركز أنت على كيزارو‬
If this is the best you can do,
‫بقوتك التافهة هذه‬
don't expect to get another shot at facing our captain.
‫لا تضعنّ قتال قبطاننا في منالك‬
Whatever you say.
‫لعلّك محق‬
You're still an Emperor's right-hand man.
‫لكن بصفتك أشدّ أفراد طاقم إمبراطورٍ فيستحق عناء قتلك‬
Seems like...
‫الظاهر أني...‬
I'm falling toward the ocean.
‫سأسقط في المحيط‬
Sacred Yasakani Jewel.
‫جوهرة اليشم المقدسة‬
– Sacred Murakumo Sword.
‫نصل غيوم النعيم‬
Ouch! That smarts!
‫آهٍ يا عيني‬
Gum-Gum...
‫فاكهة المطاط‬
Dawn...
‫السوط الأبيض‬
It didn't work!
‫لم تصبه‬
Was it a holo-holo?!
‫أهو هولوهولو؟‬
So shiny!
‫براقٌ يعمي العين‬
Whoopsie!
‫ويحي‬
This again?
‫تضخَّمتَ ثانيةً...‬
Well, that's fine. A bigger target makes my job easier.
‫وإن كان هذا يصب في صالحي، فكلمّا كبر الهدف سَهُلَت إصابته‬
Which one's real?!
‫أيُّهم الحقيقي؟‬
Just kidding!
‫أمزح‬
Tricked ya!
‫كدتُ بك‬
Gum-Gum...
‫فاكهة المطاط‬
Dawn...
‫الدهس الأبيض‬
Did I get the real one too?
‫أنلتُ من الحقيقي؟‬
I'm the one who got tricked!
‫أنا من كِيدَ به!‬
Now, that's strange.
‫عجيبٌ أمره‬
Where did Vegapunk go?
‫أين ذهب فيغابانك؟‬
Could you tell me?
‫هلّا أخبرتموني‬
L-Luffy!
‫لـ-لوفي!‬
Apple Gramps!
‫عجوز التفاحة!‬
Wait! Let me in, Vegapunk!
‫تريث، سأرافقكما يا فيغابانك‬
What's going on?!
‫ما الأمر؟‬
You seem pissed!
‫لمَ على محياك الغضب؟‬
You better keep your hands off her, you lousy Marines!
‫كفّوا أيديكم عنها يا ملاعين البحرية‬
I'm coming to save you, Bonney!
‫إني ماضٍ لإنقاذكِ يا بوني‬
How could I leave that innocent child to die?!
‫فكيف لي أن أغفل عن طفلةٍ في حالتها؟‬
Innocent child?
‫طفلة؟‬
Get in already!
‫عجِّل وادخل‬
I'll let you ride with us! Just squeeze yourself in wherever!
‫أسمح لك بمرافقتنا، احشر نفسك‬
Squeeze myself in?
‫أحشر نفسي؟‬
What are you doing?! Stay in the lab!
‫ماذا دهاك؟ لا تخرج‬
You're gonna get yourself killed!
‫ستُقتل!‬
Where do you think you're going...
‫أين تحسب نفسك ذاهبًا...‬
Vegapunk?
‫يا فيغابانك؟‬
Crap, crap, crap! We gotta move, Stella!
‫ويلنا يا ستيلا‬
He's back already?!
‫هل عاد؟‬
Stella?!
‫ستيلا؟‬
Lilith!
‫ليليث!‬
Use the General Franky to carry the ship!
‫احملي السفينة بالجنرال فرانكي‬
I'll catch this ride and meet you there!
‫أما أنا فسأركب معهم‬
You got it!
‫لك ذلك‬
Edison! Now!
‫آن الأوان يا إديسون!‬
Comin' right up!
‫استجيبي أيتها القبة الحدودية‬
partially deactivatin'!
‫سأعطل جزءًا منها‬
Initiatin' reactivation!
‫وها أنا أغلقه‬
We're falling! We're falling!
‫هوينا هويًا!‬
H-Hey, look!
‫أتصدق عيناي؟‬
Wait a second...
‫تمهّلوا...‬
I-I thought so... That's...
‫إ-إن ذلك حقًّا...‬
Dr. Vegapunk!
‫الدكتور فيغابانك!‬
Off the Coast of Egghead
‫عند ساحل إيغهيد‬
This is the Fabriophase team on the island!
‫معكم فرقة طابق المختبر‬
I have a report!
‫هاكم تقريرنا‬
Dr. Vegapunk is descending from the Labophase!
‫نزل الدكتور فيغابانك من طابق المختبر‬
Prepare to attack! Aim!
‫استعدوا وصوّبوا عليه!‬
Attention, all pacifista!
‫يا جميع الباشيفيستا!‬
Vegapunk has new orders for you!
‫إليكم أوامر جديدة من فيغابانك‬
Wipe out every Marine...
‫كلَّ ثلَّةٍ من البحرية...‬
on this entire island!
‫أبيدوها على بكرة أبيها!‬
Oh no...
‫ويلنا...‬
It's our turn now...
‫صرنا الطرائد...‬
Objective updated.
‫تغيّر الهدف‬
Wipe out all Marines.
‫أبيدوا البحرية‬
Get away from the pacifista!
‫لا تقربوا الباشيفيستا‬
Vegapunk must have overridden their orders!
‫تبًّا لفيغابانك، أبدّل أوامرهم؟‬
Shit! I can't believe we lost the pacifista!
‫تبًّا، فقدنا السيطرة على الباشيفيستا‬
Damn you, Vegapunk!
‫تبًّا لك يا فيغابانك!‬
That's the stuff, pacifista!
‫عليكم بهم أيها الباشيفيستا!‬
Keep givin' 'em hell!
‫أمطروهم بالهجمات!‬
Looks like it worked!
‫أفلحت خطتنا‬
Yeah!
‫أجل‬
Hey!
‫مهلًا‬
How are we going straight down?!
‫كيف نهبط عموديًا؟‬
Shouldn't we be falling?!
‫ألم نفقد التحكم؟‬
A property of island clouds is that they stick to each other.
‫الغيوم البرية لها خاصية الالتصاق ببعضها‬
The tires on the Vegatank are made of island clouds, so it won't fall!
‫وإطارات دبابة فيغا من الغيوم فلن تسقط‬
But enough about that. Atlas! Locate Bonney!
‫دعنا من هذا، ويا أطلس ابحثي عن بوني‬
She must feel alone and scared!
‫لعلّها مرتعبة وحدها‬
Bonney!
‫بوني!‬
Where are you?! Bonney!
‫أين أنتِ يا بوني؟‬
Bonney...!
‫بوني!‬
I have to focus!
‫عليَّ التركيز‬
Feel her essence!
‫استشعرها!‬
I have to give Bonney...
‫بروحي وفؤادي سأبحث عن الآنسة بوني‬
I got a ping on my lady-dar!
‫التقط لاقط السيدات إشارة‬
I found her!
‫وجدتها!‬
Where is she?!
‫أين هي؟‬
All I see are Marines!
‫لا أرى إلا رجال البحرية‬
Are you sure, Sanji?!
‫أمُتيقن يا سانجي؟‬
Has my radar ever been wrong?!
‫أأخطأ لاقطي قبلًا؟‬
Well, no...
‫لا أظن...‬
Scientific or not... I'll trust you anyway!
‫سأثق بلاقطك وإن كان منافٍ للعلم‬
Appreciate that!
‫أشكرك‬
Although, this tank...
‫لكن هذه الدبابة...‬
is too slow to keep up with my impatient heart!
‫لا تُجاري فؤادي المتلهّف‬
I'll be right there, Bonney!
‫سآتيكِ حالًا يا بوني-تشان‬
What a relief...
‫اطمئنت...‬
The pacifista are on our side again.
‫عادوا الباشيفيستا في صفنا‬
I finally found you!
‫وجدتكِ أخيرًا‬
The pirate... Jewelry Bonney!
‫أيتها القرصانة جولري بوني‬
Vice Admiral Pomsky Marine Headquarters
‫بومسكي‬ ‫نائب أميرال من مقر البحرية‬
How dare you do that to my men!
‫ويلكِ لما فعلتِ برجالي‬
Found her! She's over here!
‫وجدتها، إنها هناك‬
Near-Death Experience!
‫على شفا الموت‬
Hey! What happened to you guys?!
‫ما بلاكم يا رجال؟‬
I saw the river Styx...
‫رأيتُ الموت بأمّ عيني‬
Get back here, Bonney!
‫الزمي مكانكِ يا بوني!‬
You will not escape!
‫لن تهربي‬
Why?!
‫لمَ؟‬
It might be just the one, but I can control it no matter what the authority hierarchy says!
‫يكفيني أن أسيطر على إحدى الوحدات لأقطع تسلسل الأوامر عليها‬
I command anything I ride!
‫إني آمر ما أمطيته‬
Vice Admiral Bluegrass Marine Headquarters
‫نائب أميرال في مقر البحرية‬ ‫بلوغراس‬
I'm a driver lady who ate the Ride-Ride Fruit!
‫فأنا آكلة فاكهة الامتطاء‬
If I kill you, will it lift the curse you placed on our men?!
‫هل بقتلكِ تُبطل اللعنة التي وضعتِها على الجنود؟‬
Dad...
‫أبي...‬
Give them back their proper ages!
‫أعيدي إليهم أعمارهم الحقة‬
Bonney, you need to pay attention!
‫لا تشردي يا بوني-تشان‬
Black Leg!
‫الساق السوداء!‬
Y'know, I heard Kuma is your father.
‫سمعتُ أن كوما والدكِ‬
But you have to remember those aren't him! Or else you...
‫ولكن إذا لم تعزمي أمركِ فإنكِ...‬
Otter Hammer!
‫مطرقة القضاعة‬
They just keep coming!
‫ما إن فتكنا بواحدٍ أتى آخر...‬
Guess we should run for it!
‫فيكفينا الهرب منهم‬
Don't let them escape, pacifista!
‫لا يفرّا منك أيها الباشيفيستا!‬
What?!
‫ماذا؟‬
Bonney!
‫بوني!‬
Sanji, Bonney! Get in!
‫اركبا يا سانجي-كن ويا بوني‬
The pacifista are on our side now! Let's head back up!
‫الباشيفيستا في صفِّنا حاليًّا، لنعد إلى الأعلى‬
Shake it off already!
‫خلّصنا منه حالًا‬
Labophase
‫طابق المختبر‬
There's no use resisting!
‫لا جدوى من المقاومة‬
You don't stand a chance!
‫فلن تقدروا على هزيمتا‬
This guy never learns.
‫لا أظنه اتعظ‬
We have our own reasons for doing this too, you know.
‫لأفعالنا مسوّغات‬
Don't care!
‫لا يهمنا!‬
This is the end of the line for you guys!
‫هذه نهايتكم أجمعين‬
You can bark all you want!
‫العواء آخر مبلغك‬
Apologies, but if I spend all my time on you, I won't be able to complete my mission.
‫اعذرني، اعذرني، فلن أُتمّ مهمتي إن لم أُجهِز عليك حالًا‬
That's the idea!
‫وهذه...‬
My mission is to waste your time!
‫مهمتي أنا‬
What to do...?
‫يا للمعضلة‬
Hold it!
‫لا تبرح مكانك‬
What's the matter, Chopper?
‫ما الخطب يا تشوبر؟‬
Well...
‫حسنٌ...‬
I'm not sure what it is, but...
‫يراودني شعورٌ مبهم‬
What is this haunting presence?
‫ما هذا الحضور المهيب؟‬
What in the world...?
‫يا ويلنا!‬
Stand down, pacifista.
‫توقفوا أيها الباشيفيستا‬
What?!
‫ما هذا؟‬
The pacifista have stopped escorting us!
‫توقفوا الباشيفيستا عن حراستنا‬
Come on, pacifista!
‫تحركوا أيها الباشيفيستا‬
You're supposed to keep us safe!
‫احمونا!‬
I gave you an order!
‫نفذوا أمري!‬
What's up with this?!
‫ما الخطب؟‬
The only ones above us in the authority hierarchy...
‫لا يعلونا في الصلاحية...‬
are...
‫إلا...‬
the Five Elders!
‫الشيوخ الخمسة!‬
Are we under attack?!
‫أيهاجم العدو؟‬
A summoning circle?!
‫دائرة سحرية؟‬
What the hell?!
‫ما هذا؟‬
Something's off! We need to get to higher ground!
‫هذا غريب، لنسرع إلى الأعلى‬
Right!
‫أبشر‬
Attention, all Marines on land!
‫إلى بحرية الجزيرة‬
St. Saturn of the Five Elders will make landfall on Egghead shortly!
‫الشيخ القديس ساترن سيترجل إلى إيغهيد عاجلًا‬
No one below the rank of commodore is permitted to behold him!
‫لا يسمح لمن دون رتبة العميد برؤيته‬
An Elder?!
‫أقال شيخ؟‬
I repeat!
‫أكرر:‬
St. Saturn of the Five Elders will make landfall on Egghead shortly!
‫الشيخ القديس ساترن سيترجل إلى إيغهيد عاجلًا‬
What the hell is up with that explosion?!
‫ما ذلك الانفجار؟‬
The Five Elders?! One of them came all the way to the island?!
‫أقال شيخ؟ أتى أحدهم إلى هذه الجزيرة حقًّا؟‬
"Five Elders"?!
‫شيخ؟‬
Who the hell are they?!
‫وما الشيوخ؟‬
Only the highest authority in the world!
‫أعلى سلطة في العالم!‬
What?!
‫ماذا؟!‬
Something's coming out...!
‫ثمَّة ما يخرج‬
What is that?!
‫ما هذا؟‬
It's a monster...!
‫لا أراه إلا وحشًا‬
Don't say that!
‫أحجم عن قولك!‬
It has to be...
‫لا ريب في أنه...‬
The surface...
‫السطح...‬
It has been a while...
‫لم أطأه منذ زمن‬
St. Jaygarcia Saturn Godhead of Science and Defense Five Elders, Highest Authority of the World Government
‫السلطة العليا في حكومة العالم‬ ‫أحد الشيوخ الخمسة‬ ‫إله الحرب الموكل بالدفاع العلمي‬ ‫القديس جاي غارسيا ساترن‬
Is that some kind of monster?!
‫ما ذاك الوحش؟‬
Look up!
‫في الأعلى!‬
Swerve!
‫تفادوه!‬
Oops...
‫ويحي...‬
That was close...
‫كدتُ أصبه...‬
Oh no! The island clouds...!
‫ويلنا، إن الغيوم البرية...‬
Kizaru!
‫كيزارو!‬
Hold it right there, Kizaru!
‫انتظر يا كيزارو!‬
You have to be reaching your limit with that form by now...
‫ألم تبلغ حدك في هيئتك هذه؟‬
Please, Luffy!
‫نرجوك يا لوفي‬
Do something!
‫تصرّف!‬
I'm on it–
‫اتّكلوا...‬
Gum-Gum...
‫فاكهة المطاط‬
Star...
‫مدفع النجم الأبيض‬
Well now... this isn't good.
‫هذه... مُهلكة...‬
Nika...
‫نيكا...‬
Time's up...
‫بلغتُ حدي...‬
Are you okay, Vegapunk?!
‫أأنت بخير يا فيغابانك؟‬
Not to worry, I'm alright.
‫لا تقلق علي‬
Atlas, are you hurt?!
‫أطالكِ أذًى يا أطلس؟‬
I'm fine!
‫كلّي بخير‬
Are you St. Saturn?
‫أأنت القديس ساترن؟‬
Indeed I am.
‫بشحمه ولحمه‬
I was certain we had killed you already, Vegapunk.
‫حسبتُكَ قد قُتِلتَ يا فيغابانك‬
I gave you an order, Vegapunk.
‫قد أمرتك يا فيغابانك‬
Bonney!
‫بوني-تشان!‬
You are not to leave him an ounce of free will!
‫بألَّا تبقي ذرةً من وعيه‬
But if I do that, then Kuma...
‫ولكن بذلك كوما...‬
St. Saturn!
‫القديس ساترن!‬